const interviewQuestions = {
    "questions": [

        // Software Engineer
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Software Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"A software engineer is a person who applies the principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of computer software.",
            "question": "What is Software Engineering?",
            "answer": "Software Engineering is a process of developing a software product in a well-defined systematic approach. In other words, developing a software by using scientific principles, methods, and procedures.",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Software Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"A software engineer is a person who applies the principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of computer software.",
            "question": "What is Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC)?",
            "answer": "SDLC defines a set of guidelines to develop a software product. SDLC has different phases namely: Gathering Requirements, Analysis, Planning, Development, Testing, Implementation, Maintenance, and Documentation.",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Software Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"A software engineer is a person who applies the principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of computer software.",
            "question": "Explain the role of a Software Project Manager.",
            "answer": "A Project Manager is responsible for driving the software project in a systematic approach. Some of the key roles & responsibilities of a software project manager include project planning, tracking the progress of the project, risk management, resource management, execution of development activities, delivering the project under cost, time and quality constraints.",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Software Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"A software engineer is a person who applies the principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of computer software.",
            "question": "What is the difference between stack and queue?",
            "answer": "Queue is always first in, first out. Stack is always last in, first out",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Software Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"A software engineer is a person who applies the principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing, and evaluation of computer software.",
            "question": "What is Software Project Estimation?",
            "answer": "Project Estimation is a process utilized to calculate the development costs such as effort, time and resources required to deliver a project.",
        },

        // Automotive Engineer
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Automotive Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"Automotive engineering is a branch of vehicle engineering, incorporating elements of mechanical, electrical, electronic, software, and safety engineering as applied to the design, manufacture and operation of motorcycles, automobiles, and trucks and their respective engineering subsystems. It also includes modification of vehicles and manufacturing domain deals with the creation and assembling the whole parts of automobiles is also included in it.",
            "question": "What is Automotive Engineering?",
            "answer": "The development of passenger cars, trucks, buses, motorcycles or off-road vehicles. They design new products or modify existing ones, and troubleshoot and solve engineering problems.",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Automotive Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"Automotive engineering is a branch of vehicle engineering, incorporating elements of mechanical, electrical, electronic, software, and safety engineering as applied to the design, manufacture and operation of motorcycles, automobiles, and trucks and their respective engineering subsystems. It also includes modification of vehicles and manufacturing domain deals with the creation and assembling the whole parts of automobiles is also included in it.",
            "question": "How does humidity affect cooling for a radiator? A person?",
            "answer": "Radiator cools more efficiently during high-humidity because it does not rely on evaporative cooling. A person cools less efficiently because the body relies on evaporative cooling and when the air high a high umidity content evaporation occurs slowly.",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Automotive Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"Automotive engineering is a branch of vehicle engineering, incorporating elements of mechanical, electrical, electronic, software, and safety engineering as applied to the design, manufacture and operation of motorcycles, automobiles, and trucks and their respective engineering subsystems. It also includes modification of vehicles and manufacturing domain deals with the creation and assembling the whole parts of automobiles is also included in it.",
            "question": "Explain how you can keep your car in good condition?",
            "answer": "Regular check-up of parts  like the battery, tires and brakes fluid levels ( coolant, washer fluid, brake fluid, oil, power steering, etc.) fuel filters and injector belts and hose alternator lubrication of wheel bearing and ball joints",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Automotive Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"Automotive engineering is a branch of vehicle engineering, incorporating elements of mechanical, electrical, electronic, software, and safety engineering as applied to the design, manufacture and operation of motorcycles, automobiles, and trucks and their respective engineering subsystems. It also includes modification of vehicles and manufacturing domain deals with the creation and assembling the whole parts of automobiles is also included in it.",
            "question": "How often does a car requires services?",
            "answer": "Car requires services yearly and major maintenance at 6,000 miles.",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Automotive Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"Automotive engineering is a branch of vehicle engineering, incorporating elements of mechanical, electrical, electronic, software, and safety engineering as applied to the design, manufacture and operation of motorcycles, automobiles, and trucks and their respective engineering subsystems. It also includes modification of vehicles and manufacturing domain deals with the creation and assembling the whole parts of automobiles is also included in it.",
            "question": "Before buying a used car, what things you should look for?",
            "answer": "Any leakage of oil underneath the car. Check any leakage of coolant water from the radiator. Check battery condition. Check whether car emits blue gray, dense smoke or a normal smoke from exhaust pipe. Watch out for engine noises, any vibrations, lack of power or any other issues. Check for any burning smells when open the hood. Check steering wheel, driverâ€™s seat and inner door. Check tires ( Edge should not worn out, no bulge on the sidewall, no cuts, enough groves to hold the road). Check all meter work fine when you start the car",
        },
        {
            "field": "engineer",
            "jobTitle": "Automotive Engineer",
            "jobDescription":"Automotive engineering is a branch of vehicle engineering, incorporating elements of mechanical, electrical, electronic, software, and safety engineering as applied to the design, manufacture and operation of motorcycles, automobiles, and trucks and their respective engineering subsystems. It also includes modification of vehicles and manufacturing domain deals with the creation and assembling the whole parts of automobiles is also included in it.",
            "question": "Explain how timing belt works?",
            "answer": "Timing belt rests on the crankshaft pulley and either one or two camshaft pulley; they are all align through timing belt. The closing and opening of engine valves are controlled by camshaft to let in air and fuel mixture or exhaust gas, if you do not have a timing belt or damaged timing,  it will directly affect the timing of opening and closing of engine valves. This is the reason it is called timing belt and if not in a good position, it will damage your engine.",
        },

        // Plumber
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "jobDescription":"Interprets blueprints and building specifications to map layout for pipes, drainage systems, and other plumbing materials. Installs pipes and fixtures, such as sinks and toilets, for water, gas, steam, air, or other liquids. Installs supports for pipes, equipment, and fixtures prior to installation.",
            "question": "Explain what is the primary step to unclog any blockage in the pipes?",
            "answer": "First and primary technique to unclog the blockage is to pour hot water through the pipes. If the blockage still remains then, you need to use other options.",
        },
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "jobDescription":"Interprets blueprints and building specifications to map layout for pipes, drainage systems, and other plumbing materials. Installs pipes and fixtures, such as sinks and toilets, for water, gas, steam, air, or other liquids. Installs supports for pipes, equipment, and fixtures prior to installation.",
            "question": "Explain what the term building drain means",
            "answer": "The lowest point in a drainage system where the interior drainage pipe meet and are conveyed into the sewer is referred as Building Drain.",
        },
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "jobDescription":"Interprets blueprints and building specifications to map layout for pipes, drainage systems, and other plumbing materials. Installs pipes and fixtures, such as sinks and toilets, for water, gas, steam, air, or other liquids. Installs supports for pipes, equipment, and fixtures prior to installation.",
            "question": "List out some of the most common tools required for plumbing?",
            "answer": "Adjustable pipe wrench ,faucet valve, seat wrench ,faucet valve, reseating tool ,faucet packing and washers ,tubing cutter ,Teflon tape ,Cup plunger ,Flange plunger ,Closet Auger ,Sink Auger",
        },
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "jobDescription":"Interprets blueprints and building specifications to map layout for pipes, drainage systems, and other plumbing materials. Installs pipes and fixtures, such as sinks and toilets, for water, gas, steam, air, or other liquids. Installs supports for pipes, equipment, and fixtures prior to installation.",
            "question": "",
            "answer": "",
        },
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "question": "",
            "answer": "",
        },
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "question": "",
            "answer": "",
        },
        {
            "field": "tradesmen",
            "jobTitle": "Plumber",
            "question": "",
            "answer": "",
        },

    ]
}